swimsuitsforall.com 2018-06-18

# 

### PRIVACY POLICY

Privacy Policy Last updated on: July 25, 2017

swimsuitsforall.com is part of the FULLBEAUTY Brands family of companies, which includes several different brands ("Brands", "we" or "us"). Your privacy is important to us and we are committed to protecting your privacy. In order to help our customers better understand our policies regarding the collection and use of your personal information, your options regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information, and steps we have taken to secure your personal information. We have created this standardized Privacy Policy as well as [Terms of Use](https://www.swimsuitsforall.com/help/termsOfUse.php "swimsuitsforall Terms of Use") that apply to all our Brands and the websites maintained by the Brands (collectively the "Site"). By visiting the Site directly or through another site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any web site not operated by FULLBEAUTY Brands to which the Site links or that links to the Site. 

Our Privacy Policy addresses the following:

  * Safe Harbor Certification
  * Who is FULLBEAUTY Brands?
  * What Information Do We Collect?
  * How Do We Use the Information Collected?
  * What Information Is Shared And With Whom Is It Shared?
  * Do We Use Third-Party Advertising?
  * California Privacy Rights
  * How Can I Access and Correct Information Collected?
  * How Can I Opt Out of Receiving Further Communications?
    * How to be Removed from a Paper Catalog Mailing List
    * How to Unsubscribe from Email Marketing List
  * Are Branded Private Label Credit Cards available?
  * Do We Send Unsolicited Promotional Emails?
  * How Do We Safeguard the Information Collected?
  * How Secure Is My Online Transaction?
  * Do We Use Cookies?
  * Do We Aggregate Information?
  * What is Our Policy with Respect to Data Collection from Children?
  * Does This Privacy Policy apply to Social Media Sites?
  * Do We Have Specific Terms For Mobile Services?
  * Are Telephone Calls Recorded?
  * Whom Do I Contact If I Have Additional Questions or Concerns About This Policy?
  * Policy Changes

#### Safe Harbor Certification

The Safe Harbor program is an international data privacy program co-sponsored by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the Swiss government. We voluntarily certified adherence to the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor framework for the customer data that we collect. Through this certification, we commit to uphold the Safe Harbor principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access, and Enforcement. You can learn more about those principles and our obligations under the Safe Harbor Certification Program by going to the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor website at: [2016.export.gov/safeharbor/swiss/](http://2016.export.gov/safeharbor/swiss/). You can also view our Safe Harbor certification information through that site. If you have questions about our Safe Harbor privacy practices or believe that your information has been mismanaged, you can contact us by sending an e-mail to [PrivacyOfficer@FBBrands.com](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@FBBrands.com)

In October 2015, the European Court of Justice invalidated the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor.  In February 2016, the U.S. and the European Commission agreed upon a new Privacy Shield framework, which framework must still be formally approved in the EU.  We continue to commit to uphold the Safe Harbor principles, and are monitoring the development of the new Privacy Shield with the goal of continuing to participate in the framework once the Privacy Shield has been finalized. 

#### Who is FULLBEAUTY Brands

FULLBEAUTY Brands is a dynamic, web-driven home-shopping leader with numerous successful brands and specialized e-commerce sites in its portfolio: fullbeauty.com®, Woman Within® (womanwithin.com), Jessica London® (jessicalondon.com), swimsuitsforall® (swimsuitsforall.com), Roaman's® (roamans.com), KingSize® (kingsizedirect.com), BrylaneHome® (brylanehome.com) and Bargain Catalog Outlet – BCO® (bcoutlet.com). FULLBEAUTY Brands offers a wide range of value and quality driven merchandise categories, including men's and women's plus-size apparel, and home and lifestyle products.

#### What Information Do We Collect?

  * We collect Personal Information about users of the Site in the normal course of business. Personal Information is information you provide that identifies you or that could be used to identify you. For example, if you register on our Site you will provide to us your name, address, and email address. You may also provide personal information when you participate in surveys, enter a contest or participate in social networking sites linked to our Site. If you place an order, you submit your phone number and credit card or other payment related information. Credit card information submitted for international orders is provided only to our shipping partner and is not provided to us. To purchase age-restricted products you must also provide your birth date. If you choose not to provide such information you may not be able to purchase products from us or access certain services and/or portions of our Sites. Personal information does not include aggregate information or de-identified information. Examples of aggregate information include data that shows how many times a product was viewed before being purchased.
  * We automatically collect certain information when you use the Site, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your operation system, the browser type, and your activity on our Site. If you reached our Site by clicking on a link or ad on another site, we also log that information. This helps us analyze product interest and improve our product offerings. If the information collected is linked to personally identifiable information, we treat it as Personal Information, but generally this data is only used in the aggregate form.
  * For international shipments, some destinations outside the United States require us to collect special import identification numbers prior to check out. This information is required to process your order through customs and deliver your order, and is used only for that purpose.
  * We collect information you voluntarily submit when participating in one of our various services, promotions, programs or surveys. From your transactions and other interactions with us, we obtain information concerning the specific products or services you purchase or use.
  * We also receive information about you from other companies, including, but not limited to information on your creditworthiness for branded private label credit card offers and products you may be interested in purchasing.

#### How Do We Use the Information Collected?

  * to process and complete your purchase transactions and provide the products and services you request;
  * to send you catalogs and other offerings by mail;
  * to contact you about the status of your orders;
  * to identify your product and service preferences, so that you can be informed of new or additional products, services, and promotions that might be of interest to you. International customers must agree to receive the information by checking the appropriate box (Opt In) during the checkout process (see also Third Party Advertising below);
  * to notify you of product recalls or provide other information concerning products you have purchased;
  * to improve our merchandise selections, customer service, and overall customer shopping experience; and
  * for third-party advertising 
    * As an example, Facebook collects certain information via cookies and web beacons to determine which web pages are visited or what products are purchased. Please note that any information collected by Facebook via cookies and web beacons is not linked to any customer's personal information collected by us.
    * Product Reviews. You may choose to submit a product review. If you post a review, we will ask for your email address and geographic location. If you submit a review, your geographic location may be visible to other users (your email address will be kept private). Also, any personally identifiable information that you submit as part of the review can be read or used by other visitors to the Site. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit as part of your review. We believe you can post a helpful review without disclosing any personal information.
  * for our refer a friend program. We may offer referral programs that permit you to submit information about other persons (each a "Referred Person"), including, without limitation, email addresses, names, street addresses and other contact information so that they may receive information and/or promotional offers. We will use and store any such information that we collect from you about a Referred Person only to the extent necessary to carry out your request, and we will not use any such information for any other purpose unless the Referred Person consents to the use for such other purpose.

#### What Other Information Is Shared And With Whom Is It Shared?

  * **FULLBEAUTY Brands:**  Individual Brands share collected information (including, for example, names, postal addresses, email addresses and telephone numbers) within our family of Brands.
  * **Third-Party Offers:**  We provide information (for example, postal addresses and telephone numbers) to certain outside companies and marketing partners so they can let you know about products or services that might be of interest to you. Your email address is not shared with third parties for this purpose.
  * **Third-Party Advertising:**  see below.
  * **Legal Disclosures:**  If we are required to disclose customer information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, in response to law enforcement inquiry or in compliance with applicable laws, we will make such disclosure. We also reserve the right to share information with legal authorities and other companies for purposes of fraud protection. In the event the ownership of all or a part of a business within the FULLBEAUTY Brands Family were to change, customer information pertinent to that business's operations would likely be transferred to, or licensed for use by, the new owner.
  * **International Orders:**  Personal Information about international orders is provided to our shipping partner IMEX.

#### Do We Use Third Party Advertising?

We use third-party advertising companies to serve our ads across the Internet and sometimes on this Site. These companies collect anonymous (i.e., non-personally identifiable) information about your visits to our Site and your interaction with our products and services in order to serve more relevant ads. These targeted advertisements may appear on our Site or on other websites that you visit. The anonymous information is collected through the use of pixel tags, cookies, or other techniques. No personally identifiable information is collected in this process. We hope you find the display of advertising to you valuable.

If you are receiving third party advertising and you do not want these companies to collect this information, you may opt-out. To opt-out, please click the following links:

  * Didit:  

As an additional step, if you would prefer not to participate in the services offered through these solutions, you can reach a larger group of advertisers with your opt out request by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website by clicking the following link:

  * [Consumer opt-out: All Network Advertising Initiative Participating Networks](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

#### California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us, one time per year, for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates (including other brands within the FULLBEAUTY family of brands) for those third parties’ or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. That notice will identify the categories of personal information shared with third parties and used for direct marketing purposes and the name and address of the third parties that received such personal information. If you are a California resident and want a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: FullBeauty Brands Customer Service, P.O. Box 12901, El Paso, TX 79913. In your request, please specify that you want "Your FullBeauty Brands California Privacy Rights Notice." Please allow 30 days for a response.

#### How to Access and Correct Information Collected?

You can update or correct your name, address, telephone number or email address anytime by visiting our websites and clicking on the My Account or Login link at the top of our websites and registering/logging in with your username/email address and password. You can also call, write, fax or email us to access or correct any of this information. See the table below to update your information with any or all of our brands.

Brand | Edit Information Online | Postal Address | Customer Service Number | Fax Number  
---|---|---|---|---  
Bargain Catalog Outlet |  Please visit My Account on  
[www.bcoutlet.com](http://www.bcoutlet.com/) |  BCO  
500 S Mesa Hills Dr  
El Paso, TX 79912  |  (888) 289-2815

  TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(888) 355-3096 

| (888) 355-3098  
BrylaneHome |  Please visit My Account on  
[www.brylanehome.com](http://www.brylanehome.com/) |  BrylaneHome  
500 S Mesa Hills Dr  
El Paso, TX 79912  |  (800) 677-0339

  TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 528-5149 

| (800) 528-5152  
Jessica London |  Please visit My Account on  
[www.jessicalondon.com](http://www.jessicalondon.com/) |  Jessica London  
500 S Mesa Hills Dr  
El Paso, TX 79912  |  (800) 441-1362

  TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 978-8798 

| (800) 448-5767  
KingSize |  Please visit My Account on  
[www.kingsizedirect.com](http://www.kingsizedirect.com/) |  KingSize  
500 S Mesa Hills Dr  
El Paso, TX 79912  |  (800) 677-0249

  TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 682-8095 

| (800) 682-8109  
fullbeauty |  Please visit My Account on  
[www.fullbeauty.com](http://www.fullbeauty.com/) |  fullbeauty  
500 S Mesa Hills Dr  
El Paso, TX 79912  |  (800) 400-5527

TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 456-7161 

| (800) 456-9838  
Roaman's |  Please visit My Account on  
[www.roamans.com](http://www.roamans.com/) |  Roaman’s  
500 S Mesa Hills Dr  
El Paso, TX 79912  |  (800) 677-0229

  TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 274-0260 

| (800) 274-3102  
Woman Within |  Please visit My Account on  
[www.womanwithin.com](http://www.womanwithin.com/) |  Woman Within  
500 S Mesa Hills Dr  
El Paso, TX 79912  |  (800) 677-0216

  TDD Hearing Impaired:  
(800) 456-7161 

| (800) 456-9838  
swimsuitsforall |  Please visit My Account on  
[www.swimsuitsforall.com](https://www.swimsuitsforall.com/) |  swimsuitsforall  
500 S Mesa Hills Dr  
El Paso, TX 79912  | (888) 241-SWIM | NA  
  
#### How Can I Opt Out of Receiving Further Communications?

##### How to Be Removed from a Paper Catalog Mailing List

You can contact us by mail or phone at the relevant address or phone number listed on the above table for the specific brand from whom you wish to stop receiving paper catalogs. You can also send us an email by going to the relevant web site listed on the above table and clicking on the email link in the “Contact Us” section. Please make sure to provide us with your exact name and address as it appears on the mailing label from your catalog so that we can identify you correctly.

We will make every effort to implement any choice you make as soon as possible, but you should allow approximately three months for mailing change requests to be fully implemented. Any mailings that you may receive during this time do not reflect your subscription status, and we ask that you please disregard them.

##### How to Unsubscribe from an Email Marketing List

To stop receiving promotional emails from our Brands or to request that non-email information be shared with third parties for marketing purposes, please Click Here.

Please know that it may take up to 30 days to remove you from our emailing solicitation lists. If you choose to be removed from our emailing solicitation lists you will still continue to receive order and confirmation emails as well as emails relating to your other transactions.

#### Are Branded Private Label Division Credit Cards Available?

Yes, but only for United States customers. Non-US residents are not eligible for Branded Private Label Credit Cards. Eligible customers can apply for a Branded Private Label Credit Card from BrylaneHome, Jessica London, KingSize, Woman Within, Roaman‘s and FulllBeauty.com. These credit cards are issued by our banking partner (“Bank”), currently Comenity Bank, and provide the holder with special offers and exclusive Brand benefits.

Currently, Branded Label Credit Cards are not available at Swimsuitsforall.

When you apply for one of these credit cards online, you provide your financial and personal information directly to the Bank. We are independent of and not affiliated with the Bank.

To obtain a privacy policy, opt-out information, or contact information, for any of the Branded Private Label credit card programs, you may contact the Bank by clicking through to the links provided below:

#### Do We Send Unsolicited Promotional Emails?

We send marketing email offers to customers in the United States who sign up to receive email offers. Our online order form contains a pre-checked box signifying your consent to receive promotional emails. If you do not wish to receive such emails, please un-check the box. International customers must check a box and agree to receive email offers (Opt In) during the checkout process.

If you are not placing an order and would like to request occasional promotional email offers, notifying you of special deals, web-only offers and product previews, you may sign up for Email Offers on the Site by going to the Email and Customer preference page, or call, fax or write us at the addresses listed above.

To remove your name from any email offer list, you may click the unsubscribe link here, or in any of our marketing emails you receive, login to your Account Settings under the My Account or Login section of the Site and email us that you want to unsubscribe. You can also contact the Customer Service Center for the specific brand.

Registered Site users who have purchased from the Site will receive standard order status communications, such as order confirmation, shipping dates, etc. via email at your registered email account. Your choice to opt-in or opt-out of promotional emails will not affect the standard order status communications.

#### How Do We Safeguard the Information Collected?

We protect against unauthorized disclosures by limiting access only to those employees who need the information to do their jobs. Our employees are trained about their responsibility to protect our customers’ privacy. We limit the information we provide to outside companies to only the information we believe is appropriate to enable them to carry out their responsibilities under our contracts or to offer you products and services we think might be of interest to you. We require that the information collected be used only for the specifically authorized purpose and that its confidentiality be maintained.

#### How Secure Is My Online Transaction?

Your transaction information is secure. We use sophisticated technology to provide a safe and secure shopping experience. We encrypt your personal information, including your name, address, and credit card number when transmitting over the Internet using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) security software. We update our security procedures and enhance our Site to meet encryption standards. We retain a third party security firm to audit our procedures to ensure compliance with these standards. All of your sensitive information is scrambled before, during and after your order is placed on our Site.

You may notice a  or a  at the bottom of the page when you enter our "check-out" page. This means that your browser has opened a secure connection with our Site. You can also check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the Site address will change from "http" to "https".

**PLEASE NOTE THAT TRANSACTIONAL AND PROMOTIONAL EMAIL AND SOCIAL MEDIA SITE COMMUNICATIONS ARE NOT ENCRYPTED AND THUS ARE NOT A SECURE MEANS FOR TRANSMITTING CREDIT CARD INFORMATION OR ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU WISH TO KEEP PRIVATE AND SECURE.**

#### Do We Use Cookies?

Yes. We use cookies to enhance your browsing and shopping experience. Cookies are small files or records that we place on your computer‘s hard drive to collect information about your activities on our Sites. There is no personally identifiable information stored anywhere in these files, and they are used by us to enhance your shopping experience and to allow us to serve you better in the future. Cookies transmit information back to our computers and to third party partners with products and services that may be of interest to you. The information captured via technologies such as cookies makes it possible for us (i) to speed navigation, keep track of items in your shopping cart, and provide you with custom tailored content; (ii) to remember information you gave to us so you don‘t have to reenter it each time you visit our Sites; (iii) to monitor the effectiveness of some of our marketing email campaigns; (iv) to monitor total number of visitors, pages viewed, and the total number of visitors served; and (v) to provide you with enhanced online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of advertising provided by us,click here. The information collected and used by these processes is anonymous. If you wish to block, erase, or be warned about cookies, that must be done through changes to your browser. If you choose to block, reject or remove cookies, it could affect your ability to use our Site. You will still be able to browse our selection, but will not be able to place orders on our Site. Moreover, by not allowing cookies, your overall Internet browsing experience could be adversely affected.

#### Do We Aggregate Information?

Yes. We collect non-personal information about how users navigate through our Sites. This statistical information is gathered in order to improve our Sites. This aggregated statistical and navigational information does not include individual names, personal data or account information, so it does not identify you or any other customer.

#### What is Our Policy with Respect to Data Collection from Children?

We take care to protect the privacy and safety of children. Our Sites are not directed or targeted to children under the age of 13 and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 on our Sites. We do not permit anyone under the age of 13 to register with us. If you are under the age of 13, you are welcome to browse our Sites. However, you are not permitted to use any features of our Site that requires the collection of any personally identifiable information. If we learn that we have obtained personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will use reasonable efforts to immediately delete that data from our records.

#### Does This Privacy Policy Apply to Social Media Sites?

These terms, in addition to our Terms of Use, apply to users of social media sites managed by us and hosted by third-party providers (e.g., Facebook.com, Twitter.com, LinkedIn.com, etc.) (“Social Media Hosts”). Any suggestions, materials (including without limitation, images, photographs, videos, and sound recordings), ideas or comments submitted to us (“Submitted Materials”) shall be deemed as not confidential. By providing Submitted Materials you grant us an irrevocable and unrestricted license to use, modify, reproduce, transmit, display and distribute such Submitted Materials for any purpose whatsoever, and you represent and warrant to us that no such Submitted Materials violate or infringe upon any copyright, trademark, or any other intellectual property or other rights (including but not limited to defamation or invasion of privacy) of any person or entity. All such Submitted Materials are subject to the DMCA notice-and-take-down procedure described in our Terms of Use. We ask users of our social media sites to be respectful of the larger community by complying with the terms and policies of each Social Media Host. We appreciate and encourage users to contribute comments that are respectful and further discussion on our social media sites, but ask that users avoid making comments that might be considered:

  * confrontational;
  * offensive;
  * discriminatory;
  * profane;
  * off-topic;
  * spam (i.e., unsolicited promotion of a third-party business);
  * anonymous;
  * misleading; or
  * fake.

We reserve the right to remove comments or content on our social media sites that fit into any one of the above categories, or for any other reason, to preserve the integrity of our social media sites. We may block further posting on our social media sites by any individual who violates this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use. We claim no liability in any way connected to the use of or access to our social media sites.

#### Do We Have Specific Terms For Mobile Services?

Yes. We may provide certain services that are available to you via your mobile phone or other mobile device if you have subscribed to them by downloading the application to your device, including the ability to use your mobile device to receive and reply to messages from one of our Brands ("text alerts"), and access certain other features (collectively the "Mobile Services"). The following terms apply, in addition to and as part of the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy, to users of the Mobile Services managed by our Brands.

  * For our Brands that offer Mobile Services, you must sign up for services (opt in) individually for each brand.
  * Although we may not charge you for these Mobile Services, your mobile carrier‘s normal messaging, data, and other rates and fees will still apply to your use of the Mobile Services.
  * Downloading, installing, or using certain Mobile Services may be prohibited or restricted by your mobile carrier, and not all Mobile Services may work with all carriers or devices.
  * You are responsible for checking with your mobile carrier to determine if the Mobile Services are available for your mobile devices, what restrictions, if any, may be applicable to your use of the Mobile Services, and how much they will cost you.
  * By using the Mobile Services, you agree that we may communicate with you by SMS, MMS, or other electronic means to your mobile device and that certain information about your usage of the Mobile Services may be communicated to us.
  * In the event you change or deactivate your mobile telephone number, you agree promptly to update your mobile subscription account information to ensure that the messages we intend to send to you are not sent to another person who acquires your former mobile telephone number.

#### Are Telephone Calls Recorded?

Yes. Since approximately September 2003, telephone calls to or from our FULLBEAUTY Brands family of companies, including our customer service center, have been monitored and recorded for record-keeping, training, and quality assurance purposes. Since November 2014, the companies’ interactive voice response system has included a message regarding this practice.

#### Whom Do I Contact If I Have Additional Questions or Concerns About This Policy?

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact [PrivacyOfficer@FBBrands.com](mailto:PrivacyOfficer@FBBrands.com)

#### Effective Date and Privacy Policy Changes

We may from time to time make changes to our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices. We reserve the right to revise or modify this Privacy Policy in whole or in part at any time. We will inform you of any update to our Privacy Policy by posting the updated Privacy Policy with its effective date on our websites. The effective date is posted at the beginning of the notice. We may email periodic reminders of our Privacy Policy, but you should check our website frequently to see any recent changes.
